http://www.upcominghorrormovies.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
UpcomingHorrorMovies understands and respects the rights to a visitor's privacy and thus have created this Privacy Policy page to better detail how personal information is used on this site.What Kind of Personal Information is Collected?Occasionally the site may hold a giveaway, where a reader has the option to enter their personal information (name, email, address) in a form to enter the giveaway, but aside from that no personal information is stored by the site. The info received for the giveaway is used specifically for the giveaway and nothing more.Third PartiesUpcomingHorrorMovies uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads on this site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you may visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.aspDisclaimerThe information provided in this Privacy Policy should not be construed as giving business, legal, or other advice. This page was simply created to inform the reader of how their information may be used. UpcomingHorrorMovies reserves the right to update this privacy policy whenever necessary and will note when it was last updated at the bottom of this page.This site uses cookies and similar tracking technologies such as the Common ID cookie to provide its services. Cookies are important devices for measuring advertising effectiveness and ensuring a robust online advertising industry. The Common ID cookie stores a unique user id in the first party domain and is accessible to our ad partners. This simple ID that can be utilized to improve user matching, especially for delivering ads to iOS and MacOS browsers. Users can opt out of the Common ID tracking cookie.Contact UsIf you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy you may contact us via form here or direct email at webmaster@upcominghorrormovies.com.If you'd like to edit your privacy settings, click here.LAST UPDATED: 10/17/2019
// LAST UPDATED
Shadow in the Cloud
3 hours 3 min
Poster, pics, and full trailer added.
Hocus Pocus 2
3 hours 12 min
Logo added.
The Vigil
14 hours 25 min
Added a new trailer.
Malignant
1 day 11 hours
Logo added.
1 of 135
next ››
// Movie Title
(2)
|
1
(1)
|
2
(1)
|
3
(1)
|
8
(1)
|
A
(27)
|
B
(47)
|
C
(26)
|
D
(31)
|
E
(12)
|
F
(25)
|
G
(23)
|
H
(31)
|
I
(13)
|
J
(4)
|
K
(7)
|
L
(17)
|
M
(21)
|
N
(13)
|
O
(5)
|
P
(17)
|
Q
(2)
|
R
(14)
|
S
(55)
|
T
(171)
|
U
(9)
|
V
(15)
|
W
(18)
|
Y
(2)
|
Z
(7)
A Head Full of Ghosts
A Nightmare on Elm Street
A Quiet Place Part II
A Quiet Place Part III
Show more
// MOST WANTED
Meet the Blacks 2: The House Next Door
62% of readers want to see this
Friday, December 11, 2020
(VOD)
The Wolf of Snow Hollow
Tuesday, December 15, 2020
(DVD)
The Call
Tuesday, December 15, 2020
(DVD)
The Dark and the Wicked
Tuesday, December 15, 2020
(DVD)
The Beach House
Tuesday, December 15, 2020
(DVD)
The Curse of Hobbes House
Tuesday, December 15, 2020
(DVD)
The Hex
Tuesday, December 15, 2020
(DVD)
Hunter Hunter
Friday, December 18, 2020
(VOD)
Monster Hunter
Friday, December 18, 2020
(Theaters)
Breach
Friday, December 18, 2020
(VOD)
Letters to Satan Claus
Saturday, December 19, 2020
(SyFy)
Getaway
Tuesday, December 22, 2020
(VOD)
The Craft: Legacy
Tuesday, December 22, 2020
(DVD)
Shortcut
Tuesday, December 22, 2020
(VOD)
Shadow in the Cloud
Friday, January 1, 2021
(VOD)
Love and Monsters
Tuesday, January 5, 2021
(DVD)
Spell
Tuesday, January 12, 2021
(DVD)
Butchers
Tuesday, January 12, 2021
(VOD)
Hunted
Thursday, January 14, 2021
(Shudder)
Bloody Hell
Thursday, January 14, 2021
(VOD)
Ten Minutes to Midnight
Tuesday, January 19, 2021
(VOD)
Toys of Terror
Tuesday, January 19, 2021
(VOD)
1 of 3
next ››
Your upcoming horror movies resource since June 24th 1999. For advertising inquiries or to submit news/information contact us.This site is independently owned and operated. Please support us by not blocking the ads.Best viewed on Desktop. Privacy Policy.
